var myQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Who won the Premier League in 2015-2016 ?",
        answers: {
            a: "Manchester United",
            b: "Liverpool",
            c: "Arsenal",
            d: "Leicester City" },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "MO Salah signed for which Club?",
        answers: {
            a: "Manchester United",
            b: "Liverpool",
            c: "Arsenal",
            d: "Leicester City",
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Who won the World Cup in 2018",
        answers: {
            a: "Brazil",
            b: "France",
            c: "Argentina",
            d: "Barcelona",
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which CSS property will not trigger layout recalculation?",
        answers: {
            a: "top",
            b: "opacity",
            c: "width",
            d: "height"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What does the === comparison operator do?",
        answers: {
            a: "It sets one variable equal to another in both value and type",
            b: "It tests for equality of type only",
            c: "It tests for equality of value only",
            d: "It tests for equality of value and type"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which choice is not a value of the type attribute of the <input> element?",
        answers: {
            a: "range",
            b: "address",
            c: "date",
            d: "password"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which choice is not part of CSS box model?",
        answers: {
            a: "margin",
            b: "border",
            c: "paddding",
            d: "paragraph"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which part of the URL https://app.uniswap.org/pool specifies the domain name?",
        answers: {
            a: "https",
            b: "org",
            c: "uniswap.org",
            d: "app.uniswap"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Which HTML element is not considered a landmark element?",
        answers: {
            a: "<form>",
            b: "<ul>",
            c: "<main>",
            d: "<nav>"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which statement is true when an HTML tag has been deprecated?",
        answers: {
            a: "It employs code that can be viewed only on a desktop computer",
            b: "It is obsolete and is not recommended for use in marking web content",
            c: "It employs code that will require users to update their browsers",
            d: "It employs incorrect syntax that will cause the browser to crash"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
]


console.log(myQuestions);